Good afternoon
Добрый день
Well, hello
Ну здрасте
Well, are you interested
Ну интересуетесь
or is it just that
или это просто
I understand correctly, I’m not strong in the history of
я правильно понимаю я не силен в истории
Che Guevara, he was against the capitalists, so
Че Гевара он был против капиталистов так
my cap worries you, I don’t see you right away,
вас беспокоит моя кепка не я вижу сразу
I just don’t see you below the nose, I see the cap,
я просто вас ниже носа не вижу кепку
therefore
вижу поэтому
he was against the capitalists, only against the
он был против капиталистов лишь против
capitalists too  I understand this,
капиталистов тоже это понимаю
but Putin is a capitalist or not
а Путин капиталист или нет
or not
или нет
If he is not a capitalist, then who is he
Если он не капиталист то кто он
Well, or who is he
Ну или кто он
What is it
Что такое
I thought you don’t react at all it
Я думал ты вообще не реагируешь это
slows down
тормозишь
Well
Ну что
who is a socialist liberal No well who is a
кто социалист либерал Не ну кто
communist who I say if he is not this
коммунист кто я же говорю если он не это
Maybe he is a drug addict  Putin,
Может он наркоман Путин
then you are like a real Che Guevarian, you are for the
то вы как настоящий че геварец вы за
tsar Yes, I understand that
царя Да это понимаю
Well, yes, that’s right Every person should
Ну да правильно Каждый человек должен
still be on the banner, it was written the head of the tsar
еще на знамени было написано заведу царя
and the Fatherland,
и Отечества
which is serious Well, yes, yes, they are on a date
что серьезно Ну да да они свиданием
photos when they run with Fidel Castro
фотографии когда они с фиделем Кастро
and hold the flag,
бегут так и флаг держат вот
don’t remember  For the Faith of the Tsar of the Fatherland, you
не помните За Веру Царя Отечества
support the special operation
спецоперацию поддерживаете
Well, of course,
Ну конечно
Dude, I didn’t doubt you
Чувак я в тебе не сомневался я по твоему
, I look at your face, I
лицу смотрю
was sure that you supported the
уверен был что поддерживаешь
special operation  I didn’t doubt the minutes
спецоперацию ни минуты не сомневался
really really I asked you to
реально реально Я тебя спросил чтобы
find out your opinion
узнать твое мнение
who is not against the capitalist Putin
который не против капиталиста Путину не
cannot but support the special operation he should
может не поддержать спецоперацию должен
be so much I think that every
быть он настолько Я думаю что каждый
person should already be in line with the military registration and enlistment office
человек должен уже в очередь военкомат
You know that in St.
Вы знаете что в Питере было перестрелка
for a place in the queue Yes, everyone
поссорились за место в очереди Да каждый
wanted to get into the military registration and enlistment office faster, they
хотел быстрее попасть военкомат
fought and then took out a gun, they
толкались бились а потом достал пистолет
really shot, they really wanted to, they just
застрелил реально так хотели только
announced mobilization, all these Che
объявили мобилизацию все вот эти че
Guvarians ran the military registration and enlistment offices in Nizhny
геварцы побежали военкоматы в Нижнем
Novgorod, too, it was the
Новгороде тоже было
last time you won’t be again
последний раз больше не будете
Yes, but Nafig I will need this more than
Да а Нафиг это нужны буду еще не раз
once  you won’t be like this anymore Yes Cool
а вот этом уже не будешь Да Прикольная
joke and who will take me from there you are
шутка а кто меня оттуда заберет Вы вы
now with me Talk everything you need to take this
сейчас со мной Поговорите все надо этого
Ukrainian from Khmelnitsky to take away
хохла из Хмельницкого забрать выгнать
I’ll go I’ll tell the military enlistment office in my city to
пойду-ка Я военкомат в своем городе
say the military commissar of the military commissar of the ear take me the
скажу военкомом военком ушка возьми меня
hero of the Russian che gevorets with
богатыря русского че геворца хлами
wild trash to the Battle
дикими на Битву
yes  And when you go to the military registration and enlistment office
да А когда вы идете в военкомат
tomorrow it’s
завтра
really tomorrow in Russia
реально завтра в России это магический
Yes, today it will go straight with you, except that a
Да сегодня прям пойдет у вас разве что
beer store near the military registration and enlistment office somewhere
пивной магазин возле военкомата где-то
today, go there, swell
сегодня пойдете туда набухаетесь там
somewhere, of course, tomorrow everything will be shorter, these
где-то конечно завтра все короче вот эти
Che gevortsy, they all go tomorrow, they
че геворцы они все завтра идут они
support a special operation, you need to capture
поддерживают спецоперацию надо захватить
and then, in short, wakes up again and so
а потом короче просыпается снова и так
every day  tomorrow
каждый день завтра
people of eternal tomorrow
люди вечного завтра
you can say some famous phrase of
можете сказать какую-то известную фразу
Che Guevara
Че Гевары
What immediately Che Guevara famous nobility
Чего сразу Че Гевара известную знати
some no the most famous phrase of Che
какой-то нет самая знаменитая фраза Че
Guevara you know what no Russians get
Гевара знаете какая нет русские свалите
out of Ukraine So he said Let's
с Украины Так он и говорил Давайте
drive in short from him Yes, some kind of emoticons
погнали короче из него Да дякую
found a
нашел
subscriber on  channel who dosin And
подписчица на канал кто же досин И
subscribed Like
подписался Поставьте лайк
and
и
write on Telegram, too,
пишите на Telegram тоже
telegram always
телеграме всегда